

# Franco De Paulo

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### **PROFILE**

After working in the music industry for over 10 years, I decided to turn my career around and dive right into the digital world and programming. I am passionate about design and the Frontend, it motivates me to be in permanent evolution and apply new technologies. I am currently doing the back end module in the NUCBA web developer full stack bootcamp.

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

La Plata, Bs. As.

## CONTACT

- frandepaulo@yahoo.com.ar
- +54 2392 561047
- frandepaulo.netlify.app
- franco-de-paulo-13509b186/
- github.com/frandepe

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Canine Stylist

ROYAL CLAN / BROTHERS 2019-2021

Canine Stylist

Customer support

**BROTHERS** 2017-2019

Canine Stylist, product sales and customer service in pet grooming and pet shop

Professional musician

INDEPENDENT 2011-2020

Piano teacher and session musician

Commissioner

FAMILY BUSINESS 2009-2011

Sales and commercial commissions

Radio operator

FM 100.3 2008-2010

Fm radio show operator, jingle maker and telephone operator

## **EDUCATION**

Professional musician

**EMU** JAN 2017 - MARCH 2021

English

FEEDBACK SCHOOL OF ENGLISH LANGUAGE JAN 2020 - FEB 2021

Web developer

NUCBA MARCH 2021 - ACT.

## SKILLS

HTML

CSS - SASS

JAVASCRIPT - TYPESCRIPT

REACT.JS BOOTSTRAP

FIREBASE